Nathan Izuora

Houston Area nathanizuora@gmail.com (321) 693-2039

Skill set:

Organized and efficient. Thorough clerical experience (professional phone etiquette, typing speed of 70 WPM, Microsoft Office expertise, etc.). Fast and adaptive learner with the ability to solve problems

and make decisions when needed. Strong communication skills and years of customer service experience and quality assurance.

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP

Education:

DigitalCrafts- Houston, Tx (Feb. 2018 - May 2018)

Houston Community College - Katy, Tx (2015 - 2017)

Work experience:

CVS Pharma Tech - Rosenberg, TX (Sept. 2016 - Present)

Duties performed:

- * Ability to multi-task and perform in fast and efficient manner.
- * Experience with customer facing and professional service.
- * Inventory management, customer notifications regarding medication changes, and quality assurance.

Sam's Club - Richmond, TX (July 2013 – January 2015)

Duties performed:

- *Customer facing
- *Inventory management and system updates

Pier 1 Imports - Richmond, TX (July 2011 – August 2013)

Greet and welcome every customer that entered and ask if any assistance or help was needed; as well as handle and solve any problems or questions customers may present. Update logged

information regarding shipments of merchandise and stock store on weekly basis. Manage the shipment log and record any missing or damaged items.